

My Contact

atifsalehin731@gmail.com

+8801744187326

229,Moghbazar-Noyatola, Dhaka-1217

Hard Skill

- Social Media Managing
- Voiceover Artist
- Data Entry & processing
- Copywriting
- Article Writing
- Data mining and analysis
- Social Media Marketing
- Sales/Idea Management
- Communication
- Basic Computer skills (MS word/PowerPoint/Excel)

Education Background

National Bank Public School

Secondary School Certificate Completed in 2018 G.P.A. 5.00

• Government Science College

Higher Secondary School Certificate Completed 2020 G.P.A. 5.00

University of Asia Pacific

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Engineering From 2022 - Present G.P.A. so far 3.53

Achievements

2022 - **Winner of Quiz Competition** Software and Hardware Club

2023 - **1st Runner up of Idea Season 2.0**Entrepreneurship and Career
Development Club

Md. Atif Salehin

DIGITAL MARKETER

About Me

Atif Salehin

As a highly skilled and educated graphic and user experience designer, I bring a wealth of expertise to the field. With a strong background in social media management, voice artistry, and video editing, I take immense pride in delivering top-notch work across platforms. Known for my unwavering enthusiasm, reliability, and exceptional work ethic, I excel in challenging situations and consistently exceed expectations. My adaptability shines as both a team player and independent contributor, meeting and surpassing strict deadlines with a focused, dedicated approach.

Professional Experience

Junior Social media Designer And Social Media Manager at Dana n Decor

2019 - 2021

- Analyzing engagement data.
- Social media marketing.
- Product Idea designing.
- Identifying trends in customer interactions and planning digital campaigns to build community online.

Information Analysis and Data Entry Executive at Echithi

2022 - Present

- Preparing and sorting documents for data entry.
- Entering data into database software and checking to ensure the accuracy of the data that has been inputted.
- Resolving discrepancies in information and obtaining further information for incomplete documents.
- Creating data backups as part of a contingency plan.

Professional Voiceover Artist & video Ad Editor at fiverr

2023 - Present

- Versatile Vocal Range
- Exceptional Articulation
- Emotional Resonance
- Adaptability to Scripts
- Professionalism and Reliability

Volunteer experience

- ICPC World Finals, Dhaka, 2022
- Brake The Barriers, Workshop 2023
- VOLUNTEER, Directorate of Students' Welfare

My Reference

Zaforullah Momtaz

Abrar Al Rawnak

Echithi / General Manager +8801723722788 Dana N Decor / CEO +46732441395